Yassine **SADEK**



Contacts

Italy, Bologna 40062 Via Circonvallazione Sud 9

+393278587274

Yassek98@gmail.com

Languages

Italian (Native) Arabic(Native) English(C1) French(A1)

Skills

-Office Pack -drawing art(graphics)

-Latex

-**Programming**: C++, java, phython,

labVIEW, blender -**Physics**

-Math -Electronic prototyping

Platforms:

Arduino and Raspberry.

Carer Plan

Gain experience and knowledge to build something mine from scratch in the tech field.

Professional Experience

2021-2022 **Just Eat** Italy, Bologna

Food delivery

• To finance my studies I had to work in the food delivery system.

2018 INFN Frascati Italy, Rome

research on cosmic rays

a full stage on cosmic rays and others subatomic and atomic level particles

2017 - now **University tutor** Italy, Bologna

University level of math, physics and chemistry.

• as soon as I took my exams i would start to give lessons to my peers.

2014-2017 Middle school and High school Tutor Ital

in math, science and programming

I started very young to give lessons.

Academic Record

2017-2022 Bachelor's degree in Physics (ongoing) Bologna, Italy

Alma Mater Studiorum - università di bologna

2012-2017 High School Scientific Diploma Italy, Bologna

Liceo scientifico Niccolò Copernico

Professional Education

2021 Blender Out of school activity

3D computer graphics software toolset

-Math 2020 simulation of Complex Systems using Artificial Intelligence Exam

Lab

2019 **Programming languages C++, Java, labView** Exam

Lab

2016 **Electronic Prototyping Platforms** Me and my Physics professor started this project together. a year

course of teaching to prototype with Arduino to interested High School students.

Arduino

Hobbies

Reading, programming videogames, drawing, video games, prototyping, movies, electronic music (sometime trying to compose some).

About me

Even though I didn't finish my bachelor's degree in physics I developed all the skills and mindset of a physicist. the price to study was beginning to become high and my family needed money; So I decided to stop, work for a year or two, make some work experience and maybe go back to university in a different tech field. My Dream is to create and develop technology, I hope one day I can be someone that gave something to the advancement of the human race.